http://bankoffayettecounty.com/privacy-policy

Our Locations:
Close
Bolivar
503 West Market Street Bolivar, TN 38008
Bolivar Hours:
3454 S Houston Levee Rd. Collierville, TN 38017
Collierville Hours:
25205 Highway 57 Grand Junction, TN 38039
Grand Junction Hours:
3155 US Highway 64 Eads, TN 38028-3021
Hickory Withe Hours:
327 US 70 Mason, TN 38049
Mason Hours:
14400 Highway 57 Moscow, TN 38057
Moscow - Express Hours:
6870 Highway 64 Oakland, TN 38060
Oakland Hours:
1265 Highway 57 E Collierville, TN 38017
Piperton Hours:
610 Mulberry Selmer, TN 38375
Selmer Hours:
15995 Highway 64 Somerville, TN 38068
Somerville Hours:
2640 Highway 64 Whiteville, TN 38075
Whiteville Hours:
Monday - Thursday: 8:00am - 4:00pm (drive thru 5:00)
Facts
What does the Bank of Fayette County do with your personal information?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income
Account balances and credit history
Assets and investment experience
How?
All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons The Bank of Fayette County chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does The Bank of Fayette County share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes -
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes -
to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
No
What We Do
How does The Bank of Fayette County protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does The Bank of Fayette County collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account or apply for a loan
Give us your contact information or give us your income information or
Tell us about your investment or retirement portfolio
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Our affiliates include financial companies such as financial service providers including insurance agents and securities broker-dealers.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
The Bank of Fayette County does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
The Bank of Fayette County doesn't jointly market.
USA Patriot Act
IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT PROCEDURES FOR OPENING OR CHANGING AN ACCOUNT WITH THE BANK OF FAYETTE COUNTY
Section 326 of the USA PATRIOT ACT requires all financial institutions to obtain, verify, and record information that identifies each person who opens an account or changes an existing account. This federal requirement applies to all new customers and current customers. This information is used to assist the United States government in the fight against the funding of terrorism and money-laundering activities.
What this means to you: when you open an account or change an existing account, we will ask each person for their name, physical address, mailing address, date of birth, and other information that will allow us to identify them. We will ask to see each person’s driver’s license and other identifying documents and copy or record information from each of them.
© 2019 The Bank of Fayette County. All Rights Reserved.
Memphis Web Design by Speak Sitemap
